ws6alert.com 2009-12-30

# Untitled Document

**Privacy Policy**  
_Last Updated: August 26, 2009_

Thank you for visiting our website. This Privacy Policy tells you what personal information we collect and how we use personal information collected at this website. Please read this Privacy Policy before using the website or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the Privacy Policy periodically to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

The privacy practices set forth in this Privacy Policy are for this website only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites because they are different from our policy and practices.   

**Collection of Information.**

We collect personally identifiable information, including your name, postal address, email address, etc., when you voluntarily submitted such information. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**

The site uses cookie and tracking technology. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. Cookies can also help customize the site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.  

We automatically track certain information based upon your use of the website. We may use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address. Your Internet Protocol ("IP") is a unique Internet "address" which is assigned to you by your Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). For local area network ("LAN"), DSL, or cable modem users, an IP address may be permanently assigned to a particular computer. IP addresses are automatically logged by Web servers, collecting information about a user's traffic patterns. While the IP address does not identify an individual by name, it may, with the cooperation of the ISP, be used to locate and identify an individual using the Web. Your IP address can, however, reveal what geographic area you are connecting from, or which ISP you are using. Finally, other websites you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those websites and their pages.  

We may also collect and accumulate other anonymous data which will help us understand and analyze the experience of our visitors. For instance, we may accumulate visitor data relating to referring domain names, the type of browsers used, operating system software, screen resolutions, color capabilities, browser plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords and JavaScript enablement. When you provide us with Personal Identification Information, we are able to use such visitor data to identify you.  

Data Analysis technology may be employed from time to time if used by a Client of ours. The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly developing. As a result, we strongly encourage individuals to revisit this policy for any updates regarding its use of new technology.  
We will never knowingly collect any Personal Information about children under the age of 13. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected Personal Information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because we do not collect such information, Company has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties.  
Distribution of Information.  

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation and we will share information with the third party websites advertised or links on our website. We do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place; or (3) when you press a link to a third party website on our website.   

**Commitment to Data Security**

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. Any emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.  
Privacy Practices of Third Parties

Advertisers on this website may use cookies and web beacons. Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies who place advertisements on our website and on the internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. Company does not control the use of such technology and Company has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about you.   
Our website and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the websites of third parties. Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Linked websites may contain links to websites maintained by third parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. Company does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such third party websites. The inclusion of a link to a website does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization.   

**Affiliations / Merger / Sale  
**We reserve the right to disclose, transfer or sell your personal information to companies who are affiliated with us in our sole discretion. If we change ownership through an acquisition, merger, sale or other change of business status, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the right to use your personal information collected from our website.

**Foreign use of the Website**

To the extent that you are accessing our website while domiciled outside of the United States, you acknowledge that the personal information you provided to us or we collected using cookies or other tracking technology is collected and stored in the United States and therefore you consent to the transfer of information to and storage of the information outside of your domiciled country and in the United States.  

**California User Consumer Rights**

In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov. For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: http://www.ftc.gov.

If you have questions about this policy, please contact us at privacy@ws6alert.com. We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
